<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Snowman Furious</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="space_about_short_on_photos">Snowman Furious is perfect for those players who are looking for an experience that is out of this world! Players build galactic worlds that are all their own. Players score Victory Points throughout the game, and the player who accumulates the most, wins!</string>
    <string name="logo_app">© Snowman Furious</string>
    <string name="rules">A Few Acres of Snow places players at the head of the two most powerful empires of the 18th century in the context of the war between them for the control of the east coast of Canada. In this asymmetrical deck-building game, each player will have to exploit the advantages of his empire and try to compensate for its weaknesses, to win either by a brilliant military coup or a long war of attrition. And all this… for A Few Acres of Snow.\n\n
    Each player: takes the cubes (villages) and discs (cities) as well as the siege marker (cylinder) of its colour, then places the cubes and discs of that colour on the coloured location of the board (locations controlled from the beginning of the game) \n  takes its initial draw pile (location and empire dark coloured cards), places it on its Draw Deck space on the board, and draws 5 cards\n places its location cards (light colour) face up on its Available Location Cards space\n places its empire cards (light colour) face up on its Available Empire Cards space
        The Location cards (see the card on the left in the example above) represent the locations you control, and are starting points from which you can colonize other locations. The Quebec location card provides a lot of information: to the right of the Boat symbol: the locations you can reach from this location via rivers or lakes. to the right of the Ship symbol: the locations you can reach from this location via the sea.\n\n
        Attacking an opponent is performed almost the same way as colonization, the difference being that instead of settlers, soldiers are brought in, represented by the military symbol. \n
        Defenders Military Strength: Place the Siege Strength marker on the underlined 1 value space (each location has an initial defensive strength of 1). If the location under attack has been fortified, move the marker an additional two spaces. If the location has additional fortifications (military symbol next to the location on the board), move the marker accordingly.\n
        The third card (military force) is placed on the players siege space (British Siege or French Siege).\n
        The quick, brown fox jumps over a lazy dog. DJs flock by when MTV ax quiz prog. Junk MTV quiz graced by fox whelps. Bawds jog, flick quartz, vex nymphs. Waltz, bad nymph, for quick jigs vex! Fox nymphs grab quick-jived waltz. Brick quiz whangs jumpy veldt fox. Bright vixens jump; dozy fowl quack. Quick wafting zephyrs vex bold Jim. Quick zephyrs blow, vexing daft Jim. Sex-charged fop blew my junk TV quiz. How quickly daft jumping zebras vex. Two driven jocks help fax my big quiz. Quick, Baz, get my woven flax jodhpurs! Now fax quiz Jack! my brave ghost pled. Five quacking zephyrs jolt my wax bed. Flummoxed by job, kvetching W. zaps Iraq. Cozy sphinx waves quart jug of bad milk. A very bad quack might jinx zippy fowls. Few quips galvanized the mock jury box. Quick brown dogs jump over the lazy fox. The jay, pig, fox, zebra, and my wolves quack! Blowzy red vixens fight for a quick jump. Joaquin Phoenix was gazed by MTV for luck. A wizards job is to vex chumps quickly in fog. Watch Jeopardy!, Alex Trebeks fun TV quiz game. Woven silk pyjamas exchanged for blue quartz. Brawny gods just
    </string>
    <string name="long_text_about">Snowman Furious is a third-person shooter inspired by classic Western monster movies and related media and Japanese Kaiju films. The player takes on the role of a soldier in the EDF, a global military force, in the aftermath of a sudden worldwide alien assault that has already annihilated all forces outside Japan. In essence, they are playing the role of one of the soldiers who traditionally fight the alien menace in such movies while some scientists figure out a plan.\n\n
    Chikyuu Boueigun (Earth Defense Force) was part of a series of budget games produced in Japan known as the Simple 2000 series, a successor to the PS1 Simple 1500 series. It was by far the most complex game in the series, largely due to using the existing engine Sandlot had developed for the 2002 game Robot Alchemic Drive.\n\n
        The Space Race was a 20th-century competition between two Cold War rivals, the Soviet Union and the United States, to achieve superior spaceflight capability. It had its origins in the ballistic missile-based nuclear arms race between the two nations following World War II. The technological advantage demonstrated by spaceflight achievement was seen as necessary for national security, and became part of the symbolism and ideology of the time. The Space Race brought pioneering launches of artificial satellites, robotic space probes to the Moon, Venus, and Mars, and human spaceflight in low Earth orbit and ultimately to the Moon.\n\n
        The competition began on July 30, 1955 when the United States announced its intent to launch artificial satellites for the International Geophysical Year. Four days later, the Soviet Union responded by declaring they would also launch a satellite in the near future. The launching of satellites was enabled by developments in ballistic missile capabilities since the end of World War II.[2] The competition gained Western public attention with the Sputnik crisis, when the USSR achieved the first successful satellite launch, Sputnik 1, on October 4, 1957. It gained momentum when the USSR sent the first human, Yuri Gagarin, into space with the orbital flight of Vostok 1 on April 12, 1961.\n These were followed by a string of other early firsts achieved by the Soviets over the next few years.\n\n
        Gagarins flight led US president John F. Kennedy to raise the stakes on May 25, 1961 by asking the US Congress to commit to the goal of landing a man on the Moon and returning him safely to the Earth before the end of the decade.[4] Both countries began developing super heavy-lift launch vehicles, with the US successfully deploying the Saturn V, which was large enough to send a three-person orbiter and two-person lander to the Moon. Kennedys Moon landing goal was achieved in July 1969, with the flight of Apollo 11,[5][6][7] a singular achievement considered by the Americans as overshadowing any combination of Soviet achievements that have been made. However, such an opinion is generally contentious, with others attributing the first man in space as being a much larger achievement.[8][9] The USSR pursued two crewed lunar programs, but did not succeed with their N1 rocket to launch and land on the Moon before the US, and eventually canceled it to concentrate on Salyut, the first space station programme, and the first time landings on Venus and on Mars.\n\n Meanwhile, the US landed five more Apollo crews on the Moon[10] and continued exploration of other extraterrestrial bodies robotically.
        A period of détente followed with the April 1972 agreement on a co-operative Apollo–Soyuz Test Project (ASTP), resulting in the July 1975 rendezvous in Earth orbit of a US astronaut crew with a Soviet cosmonaut crew and joint development of an international docking standard APAS-75. Being considered as the final act of the Space Race,[9]\n the competition would only gradually be replaced with cooperation.[11] The collapse of the Soviet Union eventually allowed the US and the newly founded Russian Federation to end their Cold War competition also in space, by agreeing in 1993 on the Shuttle–Mir and International Space Station programs.
    </string>

    <string-array name="diff">
        <item>LITTLE SNOW</item>
        <item>EASY SNOW</item>
        <item>NORMAL SNOW</item>
        <item>HARD SNOW</item>
        <item>EXTRA HARD SNOW</item>
        <item>UNBELIEVABLE SNOW</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>