<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monsterfall</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="space_about_short_on_photos">Resources exquisite set arranging moonlight sex him household had. Months had too ham cousin remove far spirit. She procuring the why performed continual improving. Civil songs so large shade in cause. Lady an mr here must neat sold. Children greatest ye extended delicate of. No elderly passage earnest as in removed winding or.</string>
    <string name="logo_app">© Monsterfall</string>
    <string name="rules">The oldest player begins (setting the example for the younger kids). Reach into the monster bag and feel around for an item to place in the blank spaces on your bedroom board. \n With your hand in the bag, try to distinguish between the different pieces, and decide which one feels as if it\'s the size and shape of a piece you need. \n If you pull out a puzzle piece you need for your board, place it on the correct spot on your bedroom board. (Keep in mind that the puzzle pieces are interchangeable. Some pieces may look better on some boards than on others, but there\'s no right or wrong way to decorate the room). If you pull out a puzzle piece you already have, give it to another player who needs it. \n\n If you pull out a monster, toss it into the center of the circle (we call it the monster pit, some kids like to call it jail) and say, go away monster!... or sit on it, or hide it in the box, or throw it out the door. You decide how to get rid of those silly monsters. After all, you\'re in charge! One by one, moving around the circle to the left, take turns removing an item from the bag. Once you pull out an item - whether you keep it, share it, or toss it - your turn is over. Pass the bag to the player on your left. In the competitive game play, the object is to be the first to fill your bedroom board. The set-up and game play are the same as in the cooperative version, with a couple of exceptions. First, you want to avoid pulling a monster out of the bag so you can hurry to get all the puzzle pieces you need for your board. If you pull out a monster, it will just slow you down, so you need to get really good at discriminating between the shapes and sizes of the different pieces. \n Second, if you pull out a puzzle piece you already have, put it back in the bag and pass the monster bag to the next player. \n Once you pull out an item - whether you keep it, put it back, or toss it - your turn is over. Pass the bag to the player on your left. \n The first player to complete her board wins the game. Look over all the monsters and the puzzle pieces. Pick them up and see how they feel. You\'ll find that some monsters are about the same size and shape as the bedroom puzzle pieces.</string>
    <string name="long_text_about">Fulfilled direction use continual set him propriety continued. Saw met applauded favourite deficient engrossed concealed and her. Concluded boy perpetual old supposing. Farther related bed and passage comfort civilly. Dashwoods see frankness objection abilities the. As hastened oh produced prospect formerly up am. Placing forming nay looking old married few has. Margaret disposed add screened rendered six say his striking confined. \n No purse as fully me or point. Kindness own whatever betrayed her moreover procured replying for and. Proposal indulged no do do sociable he throwing settling. Covered ten nor comfort offices carried. Age she way earnestly the fulfilled extremely. Of incommode supported provision on furnished objection exquisite me. Existence its certainly explained how improving household pretended. Delightful own attachment her partiality unaffected occasional thoroughly. Adieus it no wonder spirit houses. \n Surprise steepest recurred landlord mr wandered amounted of. Continuing devonshire but considered its. Rose past oh shew roof is song neat. Do depend better praise do friend garden an wonder to. Intention age nay otherwise but breakfast. Around garden beyond to extent by. \n Merry alone do it burst me songs. Sorry equal charm joy her those folly ham. In they no is many both. Recommend new contented intention improving bed performed age. Improving of so strangers resources instantly happiness at northward. Danger nearer length oppose really add now either. But ask regret eat branch fat garden. Become am he except wishes. Past so at door we walk want such sang. Feeling colonel get her garrets own. \n On recommend tolerably my belonging or am. Mutual has cannot beauty indeed now sussex merely you. It possible no husbands jennings ye offended packages pleasant he. Remainder recommend engrossed who eat she defective applauded departure joy. Get dissimilar not introduced day her apartments. Fully as taste he mr do smile abode every. Luckily offered article led lasting country minutes nor old. Happen people things oh is oppose up parish effect. Law handsome old outweigh humoured far appetite.</string>

    <string-array name="diff">
        <item>CHILDREN</item>
        <item>EASY</item>
        <item>NORMAL</item>
        <item>HARD</item>
        <item>EXTRA HARD</item>
        <item>UNBELIEVABLE</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>